So I'm going to show you the ERD that I created for
the website for Code Energy Solar.
So we have the entities right here.
The main subject of this website is to provide the users orders,
to provide the equipment, like solar panels and solar inverters.
So, we're starting right here. We have the
user entity that is holding
the id, user id, user name, mail,
password and after we have the entity order
that is holding every
one right here and we also
have the budget entity, items, structure, solar panel and solar inverter.
So the connection, the relationship between these entities is the following. So, for one
user we can have many orders or many budgets.
We can have just one order for each one budget.
We can have many items.
For one budget.
And we can also add like one solar inverter,
one solar panel and one kind of structure for the list of items.
After we added all the items we need,
we can create the budget and we can create many budgets
for one user. And then,
after we get what we want,
we can go